ink it upLet the needlefuckin' scream
Tattoo's myrebellion,it's myoutlaws Read
no suits, nolies Nobullshit in
disguise Skullon my chest,watch my
spirit rise Iain't tattoo
anarchy etchedin my damnsoul Fuck
their rules,I'm takingback control
Needle's myvoice, ink's
my prideTattooNRT, I'm alive
inside They
call it grassSay it's a
rebel's markBut my skin'sa canvas
lighting upthe dark Roses
and daggers, asmile that'strue This
ink's my storyand it'sbreakingthrough I'm
Tattoo NRT,etched in my
damn soulI'mtaking back
controlNeedles my
voice, inks mypride Tattoo
anarchy, I'malive inside
No shame, nofear, nocorporate crap
Every line'san anthem,every scar's a
map From thestreets to thestars, I'm
moaning my wayTattooed andloud, got
somethingTheirworld's a drag
full of boringchains, but myink's a riot.
It's myfreedom'sflame, blackink. Bold
horn, it's myrebel, yell. Tattoo's my
power, and I'mraising hell. Tattoo
anarchy, yetstim mydamsel. Fuck
their rules,I'm safe, giveback control.
Needle's myvoice, ink'smy pride.
Tattooanarchy, I'malive inside.
So bless thesound, let the
needle humTattoo's mypassion and
I'm never doneNo limits, no
change, justink and heartTattoo
anarchy, mylife's a workof art